MARLON VARON

Web Developer fullstack

As a web developer with experience in both front-end and back-end technologies, I have worked for two years in the field, gaining hands-on experience on several projects. At Esinergia, I contributed to the development of the front-end for the Universidad del Rosario project. I currently work at CCXC, a fintech company in Colombia, where I have been since December 2022. Our flagship product is DigiPymes, a web application that drives technological innovation for small and medium-sized businesses in Colombia.

Work Experience



Web Developer, CCXC (December 2022 - Present)

- Develop and maintain the front-end of DigiPymes using HTML, CSS, SASS, Tailwind, JavaScript, and React with Next.js
- Collaborate with the back-end team to ensure seamless integration of the product
- Debug and resolve technical issues

Web Developer, Esinergia (April 2022 - November 2022)

- Contributed to the development of the front-end for the Universidad del Rosario project using HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, and Bootstrap
- Worked on other projects involving front-end development using React, Tailwind, and Material UI
- Debugged and resolved technical issues

Education History



- Platzi Web Development School (Online) February 2021 to March 2022
- Platzi Master Cohort 10 (Online) Web Development Bootcamp, March 2022 to August 2022

LinkedIn Profile: Marlon Varon

Email: varon.marlon83@gmail.com Phone: (+57) 3102059602

Relevant Skills

- Front-end development: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Tailwind, Material UI, Bootstrap, SASS
- Back-end development:
 Node.js, Express.js, NoSQL
- Debugging and problemsolving
- Collaboration and teamwork

References

- Sebastian Moreno, Frontend Developer, Phone: (+57) 311 6492445
- Juan Carlos Osorio, Backend Developer, Phone: (+57) 310 3474753
- Brando Varon, Financial Administrator, Phone: (+57) 314 3876965